A Guide to the Episcopal Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1905-1990
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1956 (Box-folder 89-107)
- College Work (119) 1956 (Box-folder 89-108)
- Examining Chaplains (152) 1956 (Box-folder 89-109)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education (154) 1956 (Box-folder 89-110)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education--Youth Work (155) 1955-56 (Box-folder 89-111)
- Executive Board--Finance Department (157) 1956 (Box-folder 89-112)
- Handicraft Guild (167) 1956 (Box-folder 89-113)
- Laymen's League (178) 1956 (Box-folder 89-114)
- Box 90 1956-60
- St. Paul's Polytechnic Institute (210) 1956 (Box-folder 90-1)
- Standing Committee (215) 1956 (Box-folder 90-2)
- Stuart Hall (216) 1956 (Box-folder 90-3)
- Treasurer of Diocese (218) 1956 (Box-folder 90-4)
- Trustees of Diocese--minutes (219) 1956 (Box-folder 90-5)
- Virginia Council of Churches (222) 1956 (Box-folder 90-6)
- Virginia Episcopal School--includes news clippings (223) 1956 (Box-folder 90-7)
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan (228) 1956 (Box-folder 90-8)
- Holy Trinity--Brooklyn, New York 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-9)
- St. Paul's College--Lawrenceville, Virginia 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-10)
- Promotion Committee--Stuart Hall 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-11)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-12)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission--history (6) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-13)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (20) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-14)
- Marion--Christ--regarding Edgar Ferrell (44) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-15)
- Martinsville--St. Paul's (46) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-16)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's (59) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-17)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (62) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-18)
- Episcopal High School (148) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-19)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Social Relations (156) 1956-57 (Box-folder 90-20)
- Brookneal--Christ 1957 (Box-folder 90-21)
- Cambria--Emmanuel--High Top 1957 (Box-folder 90-22)
- Clergy--prospective, for Southwestern Virginia 1957 (Box-folder 90-23)
- Diocesan Council 1957 (Box-folder 90-24)
- Episcopal Churchnews 1957 (Box-folder 90-25)
- Executive Board 1957 (Box-folder 90-26)
- Faculty Episcopalians 1957 (Box-folder 90-27)
- Financial Reports--weekly--Analysis of Reconciliation Fund 1957 (Box-folder 90-28)
- Galax--St. Andrew's 1957 (Box-folder 90-29)
- Grace House Building Plans 1957 (Box-folder 90-30)
- Virginia Council on Human Relations 1957 (Box-folder 90-31)
- Recommendations of Individual Churches 1957 (Box-folder 90-32)
- Reports to the Bishop Regarding Marriage 1957 (Box-folder 90-33)
- National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A. 1957 (Box-folder 90-34)
- Department of Promotion 1957 (Box-folder 90-35)
- Promotion Department 1957 (Box-folder 90-36)
- Province of Washington 1957 (Box-folder 90-37)
- Saltville--St. Paul's 1957 (Box-folder 90-38)
- Survey--presentation of findings and recommendations 1957 (Box-folder 90-39)
- Synod--Washington, D.C. 1957 (Box-folder 90-40)
- Trustees of the Diocese 1957 (Box-folder 90-41)
- Unit of Research Survey Presentation 1957 (Box-folder 90-42)
- Virginia Council of Churches (222) 1957 (Box-folder 90-43)
- Virginia Episcopal School 1957 (Box-folder 90-44)
- Virginia Episcopal School--Trustees 1957 (Box-folder 90-45)
- Virginia Theological Seminary--Committee on Honorary Degrees 1957 (Box-folder 90-46)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1957 (Box-folder 90-47)
- Amherst--St. Paul's (6) 1957 (Box-folder 90-48)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (6) 1957 (Box-folder 90-49)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1957 (Box-folder 90-50)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1957 (Box-folder 90-51)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1957 (Box-folder 90-52)
- Buena Vista--Christ (19) 1957 (Box-folder 90-53)
- Buena Vista--Christ--architectural drawing (19) 1957 (Box-folder 90-54)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (22) 1957 (Box-folder 90-55)
- Ferrum--St. John's (30) 1957 (Box-folder 90-56)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1957 (Box-folder 90-57)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (34) 1957 (Box-folder 90-58)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1957 (Box-folder 90-59)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (38) 1957 (Box-folder 90-60)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd--Reverend John H. Teeter (38) 1957 (Box-folder 90-61)
- Martinsville--Christ (45) 1957 (Box-folder 90-62)
- Montvale (47A) 1957 (Box-folder 90-63)
- Norton--All Saints (49) 1957 (Box-folder 90-64)
- Pearisburg--Christ (51) 1957 (Box-folder 90-65)
- Roanoke--St. James (57A) 1957 (Box-folder 90-66)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1957 (Box-folder 90-67)
- St. Paul--Grace House (63) 1957 (Box-folder 90-68)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (70) 1957 (Box-folder 90-69)
- Staunton--Trinity (71) 1957 (Box-folder 90-70)
- Staunton--RFD #1--Folly Mills (72) 1957 (Box-folder 90-71)
- Waynesboro--St. John's--includes news clippings (76) 1957 (Box-folder 90-72)
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1957 (Box-folder 90-73)
- College Work (119) 1957 (Box-folder 90-74)
- Clergy Conference (124) 1957 (Box-folder 90-75)
- Examining Chaplains (152) 1957 (Box-folder 90-76)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education (154) 1957 (Box-folder 90-77)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education--Youth Work (155) 1957 (Box-folder 90-78)
- Executive Board--Finance Department (157) 1957 (Box-folder 90-79)
- Executive Board--general (160) 1957 (Box-folder 90-80)
- Laymen's League (178) 1957 (Box-folder 90-81)
- Laymen's League--permanent (178) 1957 (Box-folder 90-82)
- Laymen's League (189) 1957 (Box-folder 90-83)
- Standing Committee (215) 1957 (Box-folder 90-84)
- Stuart Hall (216) 1957 (Box-folder 90-85)
- Trustees of Diocese--minutes (219) 1957 (Box-folder 90-86)
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan (228) 1957 (Box-folder 90-87)
- Bedford--St.Thomas 1957-58 (Box-folder 90-88)
- Biographies 1957-58 (Box-folder 90-89)
- Department of Christian Social Relations 1957-58 (Box-folder 90-90)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ (12) 1957-58 (Box-folder 90-91)
- Callaway--St. Peter's--title to properties (20) 1957-58 (Box-folder 90-92)
- Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (42) 1957-58 (Box-folder 90-93)
- Stuart Hall (216) 1957-58 (Box-folder 90-94)
- Buchanan--Grace (19) 1957-60 (Box-folder 90-95)
- Norwood (50) 1957-60 (Box-folder 90-96)
- Box 91 1958-59
- Arrington--Trinity--photographs 1958 (Box-folder 91-1)
- Brookneal--Christ 1958 (Box-folder 91-2)
- Cambria--Emmanuel--High Top 1958 (Box-folder 91-3)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's 1958 (Box-folder 91-4)
- Diocesan Council 1958 (Box-folder 91-5)
- Executive Board 1958 (Box-folder 91-6)
- Financial Reports--weekly--Analysis of Reconciliation Fund 1958 (Box-folder 91-7)
- Galax--St. Andrew's--includes photographs 1958 (Box-folder 91-8)
- General Convention 1958 (Box-folder 91-9)
- Henderson, Willis C., Reverend 1958 (Box-folder 91-10)
- Lank, Betty, Deaconess 1958 (Box-folder 91-11)
- Laymen's League--Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1958 (Box-folder 91-12)
- National Cathedral 1958 (Box-folder 91-13)
- National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A. 1958 (Box-folder 91-14)
- Department of Promotion 1958 (Box-folder 91-15)
- Province of Washington 1958 (Box-folder 91-16)
- Saltville--St. Paul's 1958 (Box-folder 91-17)
- St. Paul's College--Lawrenceville, VA 1958 (Box-folder 91-18)
- St. Paul--Grace House Chapel--construction and history 1958 (Box-folder 91-19)
- St. Paul--St. Mark's 1958 (Box-folder 91-20)
- Stuart Hall 1958 (Box-folder 91-21)
- Virginia Episcopal School--Trustees 1958 (Box-folder 91-22)
- Virginia Theological Seminary--Committee on Honorary Degrees 1958 (Box-folder 91-23)
- Women's Auxilialry--diocesan 1958 (Box-folder 91-24)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1958 (Box-folder 91-25)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1958 (Box-folder 91-26)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1958 (Box-folder 91-27)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1958 (Box-folder 91-28)
- Bedford--St. John's (9) 1958 (Box-folder 91-29)
- Bedford--RFD--St. Thomas, near Big Island (11) 1958 (Box-folder 91-30)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1958 (Box-folder 91-31)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (22) 1958 (Box-folder 91-32)
- Ferrum--St. John's (30) 1958 (Box-folder 91-33)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1958 (Box-folder 91-34)
- Gladys--Christ, Campbell County (32A) 1958 (Box-folder 91-35)
- Gladys--Christ (32A) 1958 (Box-folder 91-36)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (38) 1958 (Box-folder 91-37)
- Grace House Building Plans (38) 1958 (Box-folder 91-38)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (39) 1958 (Box-folder 91-39)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd--Reverend John H. Teeter (39) 1958 (Box-folder 91-40)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (39) 1958 (Box-folder 91-41)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (41) 1958 (Box-folder 91-42)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel (43) 1958 (Box-folder 91-43)
- Martinsville--Christ (45) 1958 (Box-folder 91-44)
- Montvale (47A) 1958 (Box-folder 91-45)
- Nora--St. Stephen's--history (48) 1958 (Box-folder 91-46)
- Norton--All Saints (49) 1958 (Box-folder 91-47)
- Pearisburg--Christ (51) 1958 (Box-folder 91-48)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (52) 1958 (Box-folder 91-49)
- Pulaski--Christ--history (54) 1958 (Box-folder 91-50)
- Roanoke--St. James (57A) 1958 (Box-folder 91-51)
- Roanoke--St. John's (58) 1958 (Box-folder 91-52)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1958 (Box-folder 91-53)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (62) 1958 (Box-folder 91-54)
- St. Paul--Grace House (63) 1958 (Box-folder 91-55)
- Schuyler--Christ (67) 1958 (Box-folder 91-56)
- Six Mile Bridge (68) 1958 (Box-folder 91-57)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (70) 1958 (Box-folder 91-58)
- Staunton--Emmanuel--history (70) 1958 (Box-folder 91-59)
- Waynesboro--St. John's--history (76) 1958 (Box-folder 91-60)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (76) 1958 (Box-folder 91-61)
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1958 (Box-folder 91-62)
- College Work (119) 1958 (Box-folder 91-63)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education (154) 1958 (Box-folder 91-64)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Social Relations (156) 1958 (Box-folder 91-65)
- Executive Board--Finance Department (157) 1958 (Box-folder 91-66)
- Executive Board--general (160) 1958 (Box-folder 91-67)
- Laymen's League (178) 1958 (Box-folder 91-68)
- Trustees of Diocese--minutes (219) 1958 (Box-folder 91-69)
- Virginia Council of Churches (222) 1958 (Box-folder 91-70)
- Holy Trinity--Brooklyn, New York 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-71)
- Roanoke--Christ--Laymen's League 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-72)
- Blacksburg--Christ (13) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-73)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (14) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-74)
- Buena Vista--Christ (19) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-75)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (20) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-76)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-77)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (42) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-78)
- Radford--Grace--Women's Auxiliary (55) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-79)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's (59) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-80)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history (63) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-81)
- Staunton--Trinity (71) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-82)
- Staunton--RFD--Folly Mills (72) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-83)
- Staunton--RFD #4--Verona--Emmanuel Chapel--history (73) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-84)
- Staunton--RFD #4--Verona--Emmanuel Chapel (73) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-85)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (75) 1958-59 (Box-folder 91-86)
- Biographies 1959 (Box-folder 91-87)
- Brookneal--Christ 1959 (Box-folder 91-88)
- Brydon, Mc. C., Reverend 1959 (Box-folder 91-89)
- Department of Christian Social Relations 1959 (Box-folder 91-90)
- Church Historical Society--Austin, TX 1959 (Box-folder 91-91)
- Diocesan Council 1959 (Box-folder 91-92)
- Executive Board 1959 (Box-folder 91-93)
- Department of Finance 1959 (Box-folder 91-94)
- Financial Reports--weekly--Analysis of Reconciliation Funds 1959 (Box-folder 91-95)
- Fishwick, Marshall W., Ph.D. 1959 (Box-folder 91-96)
- Gwathmey, D.L.--reports of the Historiographer 1959 (Box-folder 91-97)
- Box 92 1959-63
- Laymen's League--Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1959 (Box-folder 92-1)
- Lynchburg--St. Barnabas 1959 (Box-folder 92-2)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd--Reverend John H. Teeter 1959 (Box-folder 92-3)
- National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A. 1959 (Box-folder 92-4)
- Race Relations 1959 (Box-folder 92-5)
- Department of Promotion 1959 (Box-folder 92-6)
- Province of Washington 1959 (Box-folder 92-7)
- Province of Washington 1959 (Box-folder 92-8)
- Saltville--St. Paul's 1959 (Box-folder 92-9)
- St. Paul's College--Lawrenceville, VA 1959 (Box-folder 92-10)
- St. Paul--St. Mark's 1959 (Box-folder 92-11)
- Stuart Hall 1959 (Box-folder 92-12)
- Virginia Theological Seminary--Charter, By-Laws, and Policies 1959 (Box-folder 92-13)
- Virginia Theological Seminary--Committee on Honory Degrees 1959 (Box-folder 92-14)
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan 1959 (Box-folder 92-15)
- Wytheville--St. John's--history 1959 (Box-folder 92-16)
- Amherst--Ascension (5) 1959 (Box-folder 92-17)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1959 (Box-folder 92-18)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1959 (Box-folder 92-19)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (24) 1959 (Box-folder 92-20)
- Ferrum--St. John's (30) 1959 (Box-folder 92-21)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1959 (Box-folder 92-22)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (34) 1959 (Box-folder 92-23)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (38) 1959 (Box-folder 92-24)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (39) 1959 (Box-folder 92-25)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel (43) 1959 (Box-folder 92-26)
- Pearisburg--Christ (51) 1959 (Box-folder 92-27)
- Roanoke--St. James (57A) 1959 (Box-folder 92-28)
- Roanoke--St. John's (58) 1959 (Box-folder 92-29)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1959 (Box-folder 92-30)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (62) 1959 (Box-folder 92-31)
- St. Paul--Grace House (63) 1959 (Box-folder 92-32)
- Salem--St. Paul (65) 1959 (Box-folder 92-33)
- Six Mile Bridge (68) 1959 (Box-folder 92-34)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (70) 1959 (Box-folder 92-35)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (76) 1959 (Box-folder 92-36)
- Wytheville--St. John's (77) 1959 (Box-folder 92-37)
- College Work (119) 1959 (Box-folder 92-38)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education (154) 1959 (Box-folder 92-39)
- Executive Board--Department of Christian Education--Youth Work (155) 1959 (Box-folder 92-40)
- Executive Board--Finance Department (157) 1959 (Box-folder 92-41)
- Laymen's League (189) 1959 (Box-folder 92-42)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1959 (Box-folder 92-43)
- Department of College Work 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-44)
- Executive Board 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-45)
- Galax--St. Andrew's 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-46)
- Montvale--St. Mark's 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-47)
- Virginia Episcopal School--Trustees 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-48)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (4) 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-49)
- Roanoke--St. James--history with news clippings and historical survey (57A) 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-50)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity--history with photographs (62) 1959-60 (Box-folder 92-51)
- Breakwell, James--of Christ Church, Roanoke 1960 (Box-folder 92-52)
- Department of Christian Social Relations 1960 (Box-folder 92-53)
- Diocesan Council 1960 (Box-folder 92-54)
- Evington--Good Shepherd 1960 (Box-folder 92-55)
- Department of Finance 1960 (Box-folder 92-56)
- Gravatt, John James, Right Reverend--former Rector of Trinity Church, Staunton, Virginia n.d. (Box-folder 92-57)
- Laymen's League--Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1960 (Box-folder 92-58)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd--Reverend John H. Teeter 1960 (Box-folder 92-59)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel--historical survey 1960 (Box-folder 92-60)
- Department of Promotion 1960 (Box-folder 92-61)
- Roanoke--St. Elizabeth's--history 1960 (Box-folder 92-62)
- Whitehead, Robert, Attorney 1960 (Box-folder 92-63)
- Women's Auxiliary--Diocesan 1960 (Box-folder 92-64)
- Wytheville--St. John's--history with undated news clippings, negatives, and various historical reports on the parish 1960 (Box-folder 92-65)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission--history (6) 1960 (Box-folder 92-66)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ--history 1960 (Box-folder 92-67)
- Bristol--Emmanuel--history (16) 1969 (Box-folder 92-68)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1960 (Box-folder 92-69)
- Pearisburg--Christ (51) 1960 (Box-folder 92-70)
- Pulaski--Christ--history 1960 (Box-folder 92-71)
- Roanoke--St. John's--history (58) 1960 (Box-folder 92-72)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1960 (Box-folder 92-73)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history (63) 1960 (Box-folder 92-74)
- Salem--St. Paul's--history with survey, also information concerning the Reredos Memorial to James C., Annie M., and Lewis W. Langhorne (65) 1960 (Box-folder 92-75)
- Staunton--RFD Verona--Emmanuel Chapel--history (73) 1960 (Box-folder 92-76)
- Waynesboro--St. John's--history with survey (76) 1960 (Box-folder 92-77)
- Staunton--Trinity--history (80) 1960 (Box-folder 92-78)
- Chancellor (111) 1960 (Box-folder 92-79)
- Bedford--St. Thomas 1960-61 (Box-folder 92-80)
- Biographies 1960-61 (Box-folder 92-81)
- Fishwick, Marshall W., Ph.D. 1960-61 (Box-folder 92-82)
- Diocesan Council 1961 (Box-folder 92-83)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd--Reverend John H. Teeter 1961 (Box-folder 92-84)
- Callaway--St. Peter's--photograph (20) 1961 (Box-folder 92-85)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (23) 1961 (Box-folder 92-86)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1961 (Box-folder 92-87)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history (63) 1961 (Box-folder 92-88)
- Staunton--RFD Verona--Emmanuel Chapel--history (73) 1961 (Box-folder 92-89)
- Laymen's League (189) 1961 (Box-folder 92-90)
- Montvale--St. Mark's 1961-62 (Box-folder 92-91)
- Amherst--St. Paul's (6) 1961-62 (Box-folder 92-92)
- Morrill, E. Franc, Estate 1962 (Box-folder 92-93)
- St. Paul--RFD--Nancy's Ridge--Sandy Ridge--history 1962 (Box-folder 92-94)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1962 (Box-folder 92-95)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1962 (Box-folder 92-96)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (16) 1962 (Box-folder 92-97)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (32) 1962 (Box-folder 92-98)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1962 (Box-folder 92-99)
- Staunton--RFD Verona--Emmanuel Chapel--history (73) 1962 (Box-folder 92-100)
- Bedford--St. Thomas 1962-63 (Box-folder 92-101)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd--Reverend John H. Teeter 1962-63 (Box-folder 92-102)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history (63) 1962-63 (Box-folder 92-103)
- Box 93 1963-90
- Historiographer--April 1963 (Box-folder 93-1)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel 1963 (Box-folder 93-2)
- St. Paul--RFD--Nancy's Ridge--Sandy Ridge--history 1963 (Box-folder 93-3)
- Amherst--St. Paul's (6) 1963 (Box-folder 93-4)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1963 (Box-folder 93-5)
- Staunton--RFD Verona--Emmanuel Chapel--history (73) 1963 (Box-folder 93-6)
- Brookneal--Christ Church 1963-64 (Box-folder 93-7)
- Montvale--St. Mark's 1963-64 (Box-folder 93-8)
- Biographies 1964 (Box-folder 93-9)
- History of the Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1964 (Box-folder 93-10)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel 1964 (Box-folder 93-11)
- Amherst--St. Paul's (6) 1964 (Box-folder 93-12)
- Arrington--Trinity (8) 1964 (Box-folder 93-13)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (37) 1964 (Box-folder 93-14)
- Pulaski--Christ--history with information regarding Foy J. Howard, Senior Warden Emeritus (54) 1964 (Box-folder 93-15)
- Roanoke--St. James--history (57A) 1964 (Box-folder 93-16)
- Garrett, Van Francis, Reverend (67) 1964 (Box-folder 93-17)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history (63) 1964-65 (Box-folder 93-18)
- Brookneal--Christ 1965 (Box-folder 93-19)
- Amherst--St. Paul's (6) 1965 (Box-folder 93-20)
- Buchanan--Grace (19) 1965 (Box-folder 93-21)
- Buena Vista--Christ (19) ca. 1965 (Box-folder 93-22)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1965 (Box-folder 93-23)
- Montvale--St. Mark's 1965-66 (Box-folder 93-24)
- Fincastle--St. Mark's--history (31) 1966 (Box-folder 93-25)
- Glade Spring--Grace--deconsecration information, etc. (32A) 1966 (Box-folder 93-26)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (52) 1966 (Box-folder 93-27)
- Roanoke--St. James--history with photographs (57A) 1966 (Box-folder 93-28)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1966 (Box-folder 93-29)
- Staunton--Emmanuel--history with photographs (70) ca. 1966 (Box-folder 93-30)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd--Reverend John H. Teeter 1967 (Box-folder 93-31)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel 1967 (Box-folder 93-32)
- Radford--Grace--history with photographs (55) 1967 (Box-folder 93-33)
- Roanoke--St. James--history (57A) 1967 (Box-folder 93-34)
- Roanoke--St. Luke's--history (59) 1967 (Box-folder 93-35)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel 1968 (Box-folder 93-36)
- Marmion, William H., Bishop 1970 (Box-folder 93-37)
- Altavista--St. Peter's--"Self-Study" (4) 1971 (Box-folder 93-38)
- Marmion, William H., Bishop 1971-72 (Box-folder 93-39)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial--history (82) 1972 (Box-folder 93-40)
- Church Archives--pamphlets--various subjects and dates 1974 (Box-folder 93-41)
- Mount athos--Grace--Campbell County 1974 (Box-folder 93-42)
- Bedford--St. John--Bishop Marmion 1976 (Box-folder 93-43)
- Sedalia--St. Thomas--history 1976 (Box-folder 93-44)
- Marmion, William H., Bishop 1978 (Box-folder 93-45)
- Forest--St. Stephen's--pamphlet titled "A Brief History of St. Stephen's Episcopal Church Forest, Virginia and Nicholas Hammer Cobbs" (32) 1982 (Box-folder 93-46)
- Evington--Good Shepherd 1984 (Box-folder 93-47)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial--history (82) 1984 (Box-folder 93-48)
- The Abingdon Convocation, November 9 1989 (Box-folder 93-49)
- THE EPISCOPALIAN 1990 (Box-folder 93-50)